# **CONOR WESTLEY**

#### **CONTACT**

26 Dene Court Road, Solihull, West Midlands B92 8DL



((i)) 07341305695



conorwestley@gmail.com

# **SKILLS**

- Good Communication Skills
- Good IT skills
- Experienced in rigging & operating theatre lighting
- Good knowledge of digital & analogue
- Excellent team worker
- Proficient in mixing and mastering
- Expertise in using various digital audio workstations, including Logic, Pro-Tools and Ableton
- Proficiency in guitar, bass and violin
- Experience in sound engineering and operating sound equipment for live performances

Musically-talented Sound Engineer with proven skills in controlling microphones, sound levels and outputs.

Musician with extensive knowledge of musical styles demonstrates relevant experience. Familiar with sight-reading and digital sheet music technology.

Professional music producer with experience in producing, mixing and mastering songs for artists, bands and businesses in a professional studio environment. Focused on successful project management and collaboration to deliver final products.

## **EXPERIENCE**

November 2022 - Current

Music Producer Self Employed, Solihull, West Midlands

- Produced and engineered albums for the bands, "Alcohol Licks" and "Esore Alle", using Logic Pro X, SSL pre-amps, Focusrite interfaces.
- Collaborated with artists to create unique and memorable music that aligned with their creative vision. Ensuring timely and costeffective completion of each project. Assisted in booking and managing studio sessions, as well as coordinating with studio personnel to ensure a smooth recording process.

#### October 2022 - Current

Live Sound Engineer Self Employed, Birmingham, West Midlands

- Sound Engineer, Olton Friary and Landrover Social Club for artists The Boogaloo Babes supplying and operating equipment for their live shows.
- Operated sound equipment and mixed sound for live performances in various venues, including The Core Theatre and Dovehouse, Solihull and Billesley Rock Club, Birmingham.
- Demonstrated expertise in using digital mixers like the Yamaha LS9, Yamaha CL5 and Beringer X32 to deliver high-quality sound.

## January 2020 - Current

Session Musician Self Employed, Solihull, West Midlands

- One for the Road, Session musician Guitarist 2021- present.
- Freelance session guitar player hired for functions such as birthday parties and weddings.
- Performing a wide variety of genres at the request of the event organiser.

## **EDUCATION**

2023

**NVQ Level 3 Music Production** BIMM British and Irish Modern Music Institute, Birmingham Music Production

2021

**GCSEs GSCEs** 

Langley School, Solihull, SOL

• English Language: 7

English Literature: 5Maths: 5

• Science: 7.5

Geography: 7Music: 8

• Drama: 8

• Btec Sport: Merit